internetbillboards.net 2016-12-26

# Privacy Statement Policy | Internet Billboards

PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT

Your privacy is important to Internet Billboards. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Internet Billboards collects, and the ways in which Internet Billboards uses that personal information.

**Personal information collection**

Internet Billboards may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

information about your use of this website, including the utilization of cookies;  
information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website;  
information about transactions carried out over this website;  
information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and  
any other information that you send to Internet Billboards.

**Using personal information**

Internet Billboards may use your personal information to:

administer this website;  
personalize the website for you;  
enable your access to and use of the website services;  
publish information about you on the website;  
re-marketing to you outside of this website utilizing online advertising;  
send to you products that you purchase;  
supply to you services that you purchase;  
send you statements and invoices;  
collect payments from you; and  
send you marketing communications.

Where Internet Billboards discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-

contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Internet Billboards may disclose your

personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal

proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

Internet Billboards will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Please see our terms of  use.

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that Internet Billboards collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which

Internet Billboards operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

Internet Billboards may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

Internet Billboards is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Contact Internet Billboards:**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Internet Billboards treatment of your personal information, please write to:

Internet Billboards: Attn: Tom George  
18704 Caledonia Court, Unit C  
Germantown, MD. 20874 

0
